Guide to the Gay U.S.A. Collection MSS.426
Fales Library and Special Collections
Gay USA Collection
September 2, 2002 - November 22, 2012
2002-2012
Fales Library and Special Collections
Humm, Andy
Northrop, Ann
MSS.426
12.25 Linear Feet 10 Boxes
The Gay USA Collection contains over 500 recordings of the hour long weekly news program Gay USA which airs on the Manhattan News Network and is distributed by Free Speech TV. Gay USA was created in the early 1980’s by gay activist and video producer Lou Maletta, who also founded the Gay Cable Network (GCN) in 1982. Hosted by Andy Humm since 1985, Ann Northrop joined as co-host in 1996. The program covers LGBT current events and issues, often including interviews and special events. The majority of the recordings are in DVCAM format, with a few VHS and one DVD-R.
Arrangement
The material is arranged chronologically. When more than one date is recorded, the date indicated on the barcode sticker is used. Paper material is arranged in the second series.
Biographical / Historical
Gay USA is a weekly news program dedicated to LGBT current events, history and issues facing the community both domestically and internationally. Founded in the early 1980’s by gay activist and video producer Lou Maletta, who also founded the Gay Cable Network (GCN) in 1982. Hosted by Andy Humm since 1985, Ann Northrop joined as co-host in 1996. Created to counter the poor mainstream reporting on LGBT issues, specifically the AIDS epidemic, the program provides in depth analytical reporting and interviews rooted in LGBT activism and history. Gay USA covered both the Democratic and Republican Conventions from 1984 to 2000, as well as the demonstrations occurring across the country surrounding LGBT and AIDS issues. The show originally aired on GCN before moving to the Manhattan Neighborhood Network (MNN) in 2001, and is distributed nationally by Free Speech TV. It is also available online via Free Speech TV’s youtube channel.
Andy Humm began his career in journalism in the 1970’s and began hosting Gay USA in 1985. In addition to his work as co-anchor, he has hosted a variety of other programs, including Informed Sources (1991-1995), a weekly public affairs roundtable, Self-Help (1979-84), a weekly interview with leaders of mutual aid groups on WBAI-FM radio, segments of the Live Wire and Thirteen Live public affairs programs in 1991, and the national PBS special, Out in America. In print journalism, Humm has written for New York City News, Gay City News, the Village Voice, POZ and Next Magazines. Humm holds a Masters in Public Health and teaches at Hunter College’s School of Urban Health where he was named a Distinguished Alumnus in 2001. He was also Director of Education at the Hetrick-Martin Institute for Lesbian and Gay Youth from 1986-95.
Ann Northrop joined Gay USA in 1996, but has worked in television since the 1970’s. She did work as a freelance production assistant, wrote criticism for a nationally syndicated column, as well as writing for Ms. Magazine and Ladies’ Home Journal. In 1981, Northrop joined ABC’s “Good Morning America” as a writer-producer and was then recruited by George Merlis to join him at CBS News as a producer. After five years with CBS, she left and accepted a job as an AIDS educator and educator on homosexuality at New York's Hetrick-Martin Institute for Lesbian and Gay Youth. Working as an AIDS educator reconnected her with her early activist roots with the anti-war effort in the 1960s and 70s as well as with the LGBT community in New York City. After four years at the Hetrick-Martin Institute, she left to pursue other activist and advocate work on behalf of LGBT issues. Her arrival at Gay USA was her return to television.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Provenance
Purchased from Andy Humm.
Scope and Content
The Gay USA Collection contains over 500 recordings of the Gay USA news program. This includes their regular programming, as well as interviews and special events. Most of the tapes are in DVCAM format, although there are a few VHS tapes, and one DVD-R. The material spans the years 2002-2012, inclusively, with one undated tape. Additionally, there is one folder with paper material relating to the program.
Related Materials
Gay Cable Network Archives
Gay activists -- New York (State) -- New York.; Gays -- Political activity -- New York (State) -- New York.; Cable television -- Access; Public-access television -- United States; Maletta, Louis P.
- Series I: Video recordings, 2000-2012
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access copies for the audiovisual materials in the collection are available. Please contact the audiovisual archivist with your requests.
  - Gay USA Great Intro of Me, 2000-2001; 426.6001; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Color, Sound
    Duration: 60 minutes
  - Gay USA First Show After Cancel First Few Minutes, 2000-2001; 426.5996; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA BP2K Last 32 Minutes Free, 2000-2001; 426.6010; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA Expo Commercial 2, 2000-2001; 426.6011; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
    Durataion: 60 minutes
  - Gay USA 15 August Demo-Egypt-Consulate, 2000-2001; 426.6005; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA 15 August 2 of, 2000-2001; 426.6009; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA 19 July Democrat Mayoral Candidate 1 of 3, 2000-2001; 426.6002; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA 19 July Democrat Mayoral 2 of 3, 2000-2001; 426.6007; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA 19 July Democrat Mayoral Candidate 3 of 3, 2000-2001; 426.6006; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA 24 June Tom of Finland Art & Pier Dance, 2000-2001; 426.6012; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA 24 June Parade, 2000-2001; 426.6003; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
    Duration: 60 Minutes
  - Gay USA 25 Wed Intros, 2000-2001; 426.6004; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA 25 July 2 of, 2000-2001; 426.6008; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA [Blank Tape], 2000-2001; 426.5997; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA [Blank Tape], 2000-2001; 426.5998; 1 media elements MiniDV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA [Blank Tape], 2000-2001; 426.5999; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA [Blank Tape], 2000-2001; 426.6000; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA 04/19/2000 Mark Schoofs Interview, 2000-04-19; 426.5986; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA 07/22/2000 Gay Les Awards, 2000-06-22; 426.5987; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA 06/25/2000 Pier Dance 1 of 2, 2000-06-25; 426.5985; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA 06/25/2000 Pier Dance 2 of 2, 2000-06-25; 426.5993; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA 9/10/2000, Broadway Cares 1 of 2, 2000-09-10; 426.5991; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA 09/12/2000, Broadway Cares Equity 2 of 2, 2000-09-12; 426.5992; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA 2000 Black Party, 426.5990; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA 2000 Sex Acts Black Party, 426.5989; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA 1965-2000 Brad Harryman, 426.5988; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
    Color, sound
  - Gay USA 03/23/2001 Tom of Finland Party, 2001-03-23; 426.5983; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA 05/21/2001 Destination Groove at Limelight 1 of 3, 2001-05-21; 426.5994; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA 05/21/2001 Destination Groove at Limelight 2 of 3, 2001-05-21; 426.5995; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA 05/24/2001, 2001-05-24; 426.5979; 1 media elements U-Matic (Box 10)
    Color, SoundDuration: 60 Minutes
  - Gay USA 06/21/2001, 2001-06-21; 426.5976; 1 media elements U-Matic (Box 10)
    Content: Color, Sound
  - Gay USA 06/23/2001 Caligula, 2001-06-23; 426.5984; 1 media elements Mini DV (Box 10)
  - Gay USA 07/05/2001, 2001-07-05; 426.5981; 1 media elements U-Matic (Box 10)
    Duration: 60 min
  - Gay USA 07/28/2001, 2001-07-28; 426.5980; 1 media elements U-Matic (Box 10)
    color, sound
  - Gay USA 08/09/2001, 2001-08-09; 426.5978; 1 media elements U-Matic (Box 10)
    Color,sound Duration: 60 min
  - Gay USA 08/16/2001, 2001-08-16; 426.5977; 1 media elements U-Matic (Box 10)
    Color, SoundDuration: 60 min
  - Gay USA 08/23/2001, 2001-08-23; 426.5982; 1 media elements U-Matic (Box 10)
  - Gay USA 9/2/2002 - Rally, September 2, 2002; ID: 426.0001; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0001)
    Original format: DVCAM
  - Gay USA 9/26/2002, September 26, 2002; ID: 426.0002; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0002)
  - Gay USA 10/3/2002, October 3, 2002; ID: 426.0003; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0003)
    Original Format: DVCAM
  - Gay USA 10/10/2002, October 10, 2002; ID: 426.0004; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0004)
  - Gay USA 10/17/2002, October 17, 2002; ID: 426.0005; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0005)
  - Gay USA 10/11/2002, October 11, 2002; ID: 426.0006; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0006)
  - Gay USA 10/31/2002, October 31, 2002; ID: 426.0007; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0007)
  - Gay USA 11/07/2002, November 7, 2002; ID: 426.0008; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0008)
  - Gay USA 11/14/2002, November 14, 2002; ID: 426.0009; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0009)
  - Gay USA 11/20/2002 - Cued to first frame of Black - please time from here! (don't rewind), November 20, 2002; ID: 426.0010; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0010)
  - Gay USA 11/28/2002, November 28, 2002; ID: 426.0011; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0011)
  - Gay USA 12/5/2002, December 5, 2002; ID: 426.0012; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0012)
  - Gay USA 12/12/2002, December 12, 2002; ID: 426.0013; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0013)
  - Gay USA 12/19/2002 - No Pre-roll, December 19, 2002; ID: 426.0014; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0014)
  - Gay USA 12/26/2002, December 26, 2002; ID: 426.0015; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0015)
  - Gay USA 1/1/2003, January 1, 2003; ID: 426.0016; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0016)
  - Gay USA 1/9/2003, January 9, 2003; ID: 426.0017; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0017)
  - Gay USA 1/16/2003, January 16, 2003; ID: 426.0018; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0018)
  - Gay USA 1/23/2003, January 23, 2003; ID: 426.0019; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0019)
  - Gay USA 1/30/2003, January 30, 2003; ID: 426.0020; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0020)
  - Gay USA 2/06/2003, February 6, 2003; ID: 426.0021; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0021)
  - Gay USA 2/14/2003, February 14, 2003; ID: 426.0022; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0022)
  - Gay USA 2/20/2003, February 20, 2003; ID: 426.0023; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0023)
  - Gay USA 2/27/2003, February 27, 2003; ID: 426.0024; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0024)
  - Gay USA 3/6/2003, March 6, 2003; ID: 426.0025; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0025)
  - Gay USA 3/13/2003, March 13, 2003; ID: 426.0026; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0026)
    Recording date: March 11, 2003
  - Gay USA 3/20/2003, March 20, 2003; ID: 426.0027; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0027)
  - Gay USA 3/27/2003, March 27, 2003; ID: 426.0028; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0028)
    Recording date: March 25, 2003
  - Gay USA 4/3/2003, April 3, 2003; ID: 426.0029; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0029)
    Recording date: April 1, 2003
  - Gay USA 4/10/2003, April 10, 2003; ID: 426.0030; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0030)
    Recording time: April 8, 2003
  - Gay USA 4/17/2003, April 17, 2003; ID: 426.0031; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0031)
    Recording time: April 15, 2003
  - Gay USA 4/24/2003, April 24, 2003; ID: 426.0032; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0032)
    Recording date: April 22, 2003
  - Gay USA 5/1/2003, May 1, 2003; ID: 426.0033; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0033)
    Recording date: April 29, 2003
  - Gay USA 5/8/2003, May 8, 2003; ID: 426.0034; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0034)
  - Gay USA 5/15/2003, May 15, 2003; ID: 426.0035; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0035)
    Recording date: May 12, 2003
  - Gay USA 5/22/2003, May 22, 2003; ID: 426.0036; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0036)
  - Gay USA 5/29/2003, May 29, 2003; ID: 426.0037; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0037)
    Recording date: May 27, 2003
  - Gay USA 6/5/2003, June 5, 2003; ID: 426.0038; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0038)
    Recording date: June 3, 2003
  - Gay USA 6/12/2003, June 12, 2003; ID: 426.0039; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0039)
    Recording date: June 10, 2003
  - Gay USA 6/19/2003, June 19, 2003; ID: 426.0040; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0040)
    Recording date: June 17, 2003
  - Gay USA 6/26/2003 - Live Special, June 26, 2003; ID: 426.0041; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0041)
  - Gay USA 6/26/2003, June 26, 2003; ID: 426.0042; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0042)
    Recording date: June 24, 2003
  - Gay USA 7/3/2003, July 3, 2003; ID: 426.0043; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0043)
    Recording date: July 1, 2003
  - GAY USA 7/10/2003, July 10, 2003; ID: 426.0044; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0044)
  - Gay USA 7/17/2003, July 17, 2003; ID: 426.0045; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0045)
  - Gay USA 7/24/2003, July 24, 2003; ID: 426.0046; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0046)
  - Gay USA 7/31/2003, July 31, 2003; ID: 426.0047; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0047)
  - Gay USA 8/7/2003, August 7, 2003; ID: 426.0048; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0048)
  - Gay USA 8/14/2003, August 14, 2003; ID: 426.0049; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0049)
  - Gay USA 8/21/2003, August 21, 2003; ID: 426.0050; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0050)
  - Gay USA 8/28/2003, August 28, 2003; ID: 426.0051; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0051)
  - Gay USA 9/4/2003, September 04, 2003; ID: 426.0052; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0052)
  - Gay USA 9/11/2003, September 11, 2003; ID: 426.0053; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0053)
  - Gay USA 9/18/2003, September 18, 2003; ID: 426.0054; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0054)
  - Gay USA 9/23/2003, September 23, 2003; ID: 426.0055; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0055)
  - Gay USA 10/2/2003, October 02, 2003; ID: 426.0056; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0056)
  - Gay USA 10/9/2003, October 09, 2003; ID: 426.0057; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0057)
  - Gay USA 10/16/2003, October 16, 2003; ID: 426.0058; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0058)
    Recording date: October 14, 2003
  - Gay USA 10/23/2003, October 23, 2003; ID: 426.0059; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0059)
  - Gay USA 10/30/2003, October 30, 2003; ID: 426.0060; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0060)
  - Gay USA 11/6/2003, November 6, 2003; ID: 426.0061; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0061)
    Recording date: November 4, 2003
  - Gay USA 11/13/2003, November 13, 2003; ID: 426.0062; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0062)
  - Gay USA 11/20/2003, November 20, 2003; ID: 426.0063; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0063)
  - Gay USA 11/27/2003, November 27, 2003; ID: 426.0064; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0064)
  - Gay USA 12/4/2003, December 4, 2003; ID: 426.0065; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0065)
  - Gay USA 12/12/2003, December 12, 2003; ID: 426.0066; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0066)
  - Gay USA 12/18/2003, December 18, 2003; ID: 426.0067; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0067)
  - Gay USA 12/25/2003, December 25, 2003; ID: 426.0068; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0068)
  - Gay USA 1/1/2004, January 1, 2004; ID: 426.0069; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0069)
    Recording date: December 30, 2001
  - Gay USA 1/8/2004, January 8, 2004; ID: 426.0070; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0070)
    Recording date: January 6, 2004
  - Gay USA 1/15/2004, January 15, 2004; ID: 426.0071; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0071)
  - Gay USA 1/22/2004, January 22, 2004; ID: 426.0072; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 1, Media ID: 426.0072)
  - Gay USA 1/29/2004, January 29, 2004; ID: 426.0073; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0073)
  - Gay USA 2/4/2004, February 4, 2004; ID: 426.0074; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0074)
  - Gay USA 2/12/2004, February 12, 2004; ID: 426.0075; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0075)
    Recording date: 2/11/2004
  - Gay USA 2/19/2004, February 19, 2004; ID: 426.0076; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0076)
  - Gay USA 2/26/2004, February 26, 2004; ID: 426.0077; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0077)
  - Gay USA 3/4/2004, March 4, 2004; ID: 426.0078; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0078)
  - Gay USA 3/11/2004, March 11, 2004; ID: 426.0079; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0079)
    Recording date: March 9, 2004
  - Gay USA 3/18/2004, March 18, 2004; ID: 426.0080; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0080)
  - Gay USA 3/25/2004, March 25, 2004; ID: 426.0081; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0081)
  - Gay USA 4/1/2004, April 1, 2004; ID: 426.0082; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0082)
  - Gay USA 4/8/2004, April 8, 2004; ID: 426.0083; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0083)
  - Gay USA 4/15/2004, April 15, 2004; ID: 426.0084; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0084)
  - Gay USA 4/20/2004, April 20, 2004; ID: 426.0085; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0085)
  - Gay USA 4/29/2004, April 29, 2004; ID: 426.0086; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0086)
  - Gay USA 5/6/2004, May 4, 2004; ID: 426.0087; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0087)
  - Gay USA 5/13/2004, May 14, 2004; ID: 426.0088; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0088)
  - Gay USA 5/20/2004, May 20, 2004; ID: 426.0089; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0089)
  - Gay USA 5/27/2004, May 27, 2004; ID: 426.0090; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0090)
  - Gay USA 6/3/2004, June 3, 2004; ID: 426.0091; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0091)
  - Gay USA 6/10/2004, June 10, 2004; ID: 426.0092; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0092)
  - Gay USA 6/17/2004, June 17, 2004; ID: 426.0093; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0093)
  - Gay USA 6/24/2004, June 24, 2004; ID: 426.0094; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0094)
  - Gay USA 7/1/2004, July 1, 2004; ID: 426.0095; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0095)
  - Gay USA 7/8/2004, July 8, 2004; ID: 426.0096; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0096)
  - Gay USA 7/15/2004, July 15, 2004; ID: 426.0097; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0097)
  - Gay USA 7/22/2004, July 22, 2004; ID: 426.0098; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0098)
  - Gay USA 7/29/2004, July 29, 2004; ID: 426.0099; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0099)
  - Gay USA 8/5/2004, August 5, 2004; ID: 426.0100; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0100)
  - Gay USA 8/12/2004, August 12, 2004; ID: 426.0101; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0101)
  - Gay USA 8/19/2004, August 19, 2004; ID: 426.0102; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0102)
  - Gay USA 8/26/2004, August 26, 2004; ID: 426.0103; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0103)
  - Gay USA 9/2/2004, September 2, 2004; ID: 426.0104; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0104)
  - Gay USA 9/9/2004, September 9, 2004; ID: 426.0105; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0105)
  - Gay USA 9/16/2004, September 16, 2004; ID: 426.0106; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0106)
  - Gay USA 9/23/2004, September 23, 2004; ID: 426.0107; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0107)
  - Gay USA 9/30/2004, September 30, 204; ID: 426.0108; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0108)
  - Gay USA 10/7/2004, October 7, 2004; ID: 426.0109; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0109)
  - Gay USA 10/14/2004, October 14, 2004; ID: 426.0110; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0110)
  - Gay USA 10/28/2004, October 28, 2004; ID: 426.0111; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0111)
  - Gay USA 11/4/2004, September 4, 2004; ID: 426.0112; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0112)
  - Gay USA 11/11/2004, November 11, 2004; ID: 426.0113; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0113)
  - Gay USA 11/18/2004, November 18, 2004; ID: 426.0114; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0114)
  - Gay USA 11/25/2004, November 25, 2004; ID: 426.0115; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0115)
  - Gay USA 12/2/2004, December 2, 2004; ID: 426.0116; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0116)
  - Gay USA 12/9/2004, December 9, 2004; ID: 426.0117; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0117)
  - Gay USA 12/16/2004, December 16, 2004; ID: 426.0118; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0118)
  - Gay USA 12/23/2004, December 23, 2004; ID: 426.0119; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0119)
  - Gay USA 12/30/2004, December 30, 2004; ID: 426.0120; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0120)
  - Gay USA 12/30/2004 - G. Steinem, December 30, 2004; ID: 426.0121; 1 media elements VHS (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0121)
    Original format: VHS
  - Gay USA 1/6/2005, January 6, 2005; ID: 426.0122; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0122)
  - Gay USA 1/13/2005, January 13, 2005; ID: 426.0123; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0123)
  - Gay USA 1/20/2005, January 20, 2005; ID: 426.0124; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0124)
  - Gay USA 1/27/2005, January 27, 2005; ID: 426.0125; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0125)
  - Gay USA 2/3/2005, February 3, 2005; ID: 426.0126; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0126)
  - Gay USA 2/10/2005, February 10, 2005; ID: 426.0127; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0127)
  - Gay USA 2/17/2004, February 17, 2005; ID: 426.0128; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0128)
  - Gay USA 2/24/2005, February 24, 2005; ID: 426.0129; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0129)
  - Gay USA 3/3/2005, March 3, 2005; ID: 426.0130; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0130)
  - Gay USA 3/10/2005, March 10, 2005; ID: 426.0131; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0131)
  - Gay USA 3/17/2005, March 17, 2005; ID: 426.0132; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0132)
  - Gay USA 3/24/2005, March 24, 2005; ID: 426.0133; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0133)
  - Gay USA 3/31/2005, March 31, 2005; ID: 426.0134; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0134)
  - Gay USA 4/7/2005, April 7, 2005; ID: 426.0135; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0135)
  - Gay USA 4/14/2005, April 14, 2005; ID: 426.0136; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0136)
  - Gay USA 4/21/2005, April 21, 2005; ID: 426.0137; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0137)
  - Gay USA 4/28/2005, April 28, 2005; ID: 426.0138; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 2, Media ID: 426.0138)